http://www.ecpi.edu/privacy

Skip to main content
Degree Programs CollegesTechnologyHealth ScienceNursingBusinessCriminal JusticeCulinary ArtsOnlineAreas Of InterestTECHNOLOGYINFORMATION TECHNOLOGYMaster of Science in CybersecurityMaster of Science in Information SystemsBachelor's to BS in CybersecurityCloud ComputingCybersecurityCyber and Information Security TechnologyData AnalyticsDigital Forensics TechnologyMobile DevelopmentSoftware DevelopmentWeb Design and DevelopmentENGINEERING TECHNOLOGYSystems Engineering Master's - MechatronicsSystems Engineering Master's - Software EngineeringElectronic Systems Engineering TechnologyElectronics EngineeringMechatronics (ESET)MechatronicsMechanical EngineeringHEALTH SCIENCEADVANCED CLINICALDiagnostic Medical SonographyRadiologic Sciences (BS)Medical Radiography (AAS)Physical Therapist AssistantSurgical TechnologyHEALTH SCIENCESDental AssistantHealth Information ManagementHealthcare AdministrationMedical AssistingParamedic (EMT)Massage TherapyNURSINGMaster of Science in Nursing2.5 Year Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN)Bachelor to BSNRN to BSNAssociate Degree in NursingPractical NursingBUSINESSBUSINESS ADMINISTRATIONMaster of Business Administration (MBA)AccountingBusiness ManagementHospitality ManagementIT ManagementOperations, Logistics, and Supply Chain ManagementORGANIZATIONAL LEADERSHIPHuman Resources ManagementLeadershipOperations, Logistics, and Supply Chain Management Project ManagementBUSINESS MANAGEMENTManagement Master's - Homeland Security ManagementManagement Master's - Human Resources ManagementManagement Master's - Organizational LeadershipCRIMINAL JUSTICECriminal JusticeCrime and Intelligence AnalysisDigital ForensicsHomeland SecurityCULINARY ARTSCulinary NutritionFood Service ManagementCulinary ArtsBaking and Pastry ArtsDegree LevelsMaster’sBachelor'sAssociate'sDiplomaContinuing EducationDegree Completion ProgramsBACHELOR'S PROGRAMSRN to BSNBachelor's to BS in CybersecurityBachelor to BSN Learn Online
Home
Locations VirginiaCoastal Virginia (Region)Virginia BeachNorfolkNewport NewsRichmond, VA (Region)Richmond Virginia WestRichmond Virginia InnsbrookRichmond Virginia SouthRoanoke, VANorthern Virginia, VANorth CarolinaCharlotte, NCGreensboro, NCRaleigh, NCSouth CarolinaGreenville, SCColumbia, SCCharleston, SCFloridaOrlando (Lake Mary)TexasSan Antonio Learn Online
Military
Online+
Business Partners Call Now1.844.334.4466REQUEST INFOChat NowApply Now
You are hereHomePrivacy Policy Privacy Policy
Updated: August 14th, 2018This Privacy Policy describes how ECPI University collects and uses any personally identifiable information that you submit via any ECPI University website or social media property. We reserve the right to amend our Internet Privacy Policy at any time and without notice.ECPI University highly respects the privacy rights of our website and social media visitors and is committed to protecting that privacy. The following information describes the data we collect from site visitors and how that information is used:General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliance – ECPI University does not actively market towards European Union nations. By clicking on any of our information request forms or applications, the user has consented to transfer all personal data to and its storage in, the United States, and I understand that my personal data will be subject to processing in accordance with U.S. laws.Non-Personally Identifiable Information - ECPI University collects a variety of information from its website visitors.  Some of this data is not personally identifiable and is collected automatically via the use of cookies and other standard Internet Technology. Automatically collected information may include, but is not limited to: the operating system used, the type of web browser used, IP address, Date, time and duration of activity, and the Web sites used to enter and leave our site.Personally identifiable information - Personally identifiable information is collected only on a voluntary basis, at the discretion of the website user. For example, you may choose to provide your name, address, email address or telephone number in the Contact Us section or a web form on our website as a request for more information.Use of information - Non-personally identifiable information is used to help us improve our site by allowing us to understand and address the needs of our website visitors. This includes making our site accessible to a variety of web browsers and operating systems. Personal information collected through the site by means of your voluntary submission, such as your name, mailing address, email address and other contact information, is used for the purpose of responding to your requests for information about ECPI University. We may use the voluntary information provided to send you information about our programs and services, or updates and other information we think may be of interest to you. Information you provide to us will be held in confidence and will be strictly used for internal purposes only. ECPI University may share aggregate information about our site visitors with business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, the personal information you provide will be kept confidential. From time to time, ECPI University may contract with certain third party vendors (e.g., marketing and advertising agencies) to assist us in communicating information to and from you. In these cases, your personal information may be used by these third parties solely on behalf of ECPI University to facilitate University  related communications with you. Other than these instances, your personal information with not be shared with any other party (except as required by law).Security of information - ECPI University uses best efforts to protect security of personal information collected through its websites. This site utilizes industry standard SSL encryption when collecting private information or when accepting your credit card information.User options regarding collection of information - With regard to automatically collected information, it is standard practice for many websites to collect non-personally identifiable information about your web browser, operating system, IP address and browsing history (i.e. what pages on our website you viewed). Any other non-personal information collected through the use of cookies, may be opted out of by disabling or rejecting cookies. (Cookies are short pieces of information used by web browsers to remember information provided by the user.) With regard to personal information collected through our Web site, you may opt out of ECPI marketing solicitations at any time by contacting us through any campus management. Or, if you wish, you can email your request to privacy@ecpi.edu.Third party vendor’s collection of information - ECPI University uses third party advertising platforms and vendors that may use cookies to serve ads on other sites, based on your visit to ECPI University.  We may collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy (be sure to include your full name, address, and email address and specify what communication you would like to terminate - e.g., terminate all communication, terminate only email communication, terminate only phone communication, etc.).Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page.ECPI University will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that a Visitor is provided with clear and comprehensive information about, and consents to, the storing and accessing of cookies or other information on the Visitor’s device where such activity occurs in connection with the Services and where providing such information and obtaining such consent is required by law. Company will ensure that each of its web sites contains, and will advise in writing each of its Clients that each of their web sites utilizing a Service is required to contain, a privacy policy that (a) discloses (i) the usage of third-party technology and (ii) the data collection and usage resulting from the Service (it being understood that this clause (a) will not be deemed to require those privacy policies to expressly identify DoubleClick or any Service, unless otherwise required by law, rule or regulation) and (b) complies with all applicable privacy laws, rules and regulations.Children’s Privacy (Under the age of 18) -  All persons under the age of 18 must receive parental / guardian permission before submitting personal information on this Web site. Furthermore, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 (this includes personal information described above as well as persistent identifiers, such as IP address and cookies, except for support of internal operations of the site). If we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible. If you believe that we may have collected information from a child under 13, please contact us via the information provided below.Parents/Guardians - Any information collected from this site is used solely for the purpose of responding to a request for information and/or to deliver the requested information. If you have a question or would like to unsubscribe your child’s information from our database, please contact us via the information provided below.Limitation of Liability - The ECPI University websites may contain links to third party websites. Links to these websites are provided as a convenience only and should not be interpreted as an endorsement of the linked site, its operator or contents. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by the ecpi.edu.s157930.gridserver website.Privacy Policy Changes - ECPI University may change its privacy policy at any time. Should we revise this policy, we will post the updated policy on this Web site.For more information. For further information about this privacy policy or to correct or modify any information collected through our site, please contact us at:ECPI University5555 Greenwich RdVirginia Beach, VA 23462Email: privacy@ecpi.edu.
Copyright © 2020East Coast Polytechnic Institute™All Rights Reserved
Contact UsLibrarySmartScheduleCareers at ECPIOnline PaymentsPrivacySitemap
